<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>TEXEL, 1 Jan.,Z.Z.W.; Hawk, _ Huil. - Helge, S., Dantzign. Rott., heeft 2 dezer de reis voortgezet. ZOLTKAMP, 29 Dcc; Verwisseling, Dood, Burnt-Eiland. HELLEVOETSLUIS, 2 Jan.; Bastiaan Pot, Zetteler, Bat. 1. v. Brouwersh. - Magnot, S., Londen. - Ida, S., Liverpool. - Windsor, S., Leith. - William Conlman, S., Goole. - Niobe, S., Koningsberg. - Gosforth, S., Dantzig. - Brownlow, S., id., 1. v. Brouwersh. BRIELLE, 2 Jan., Z.W.; Batavier, 8., Londen. - Waterloo, S., id. BROUWERSHAVEN, 2 Jan., Z.W.; Alexander Newsky, Perrigo, Sunderl. n. Middelb., als bijlegger. - Baron Etvos, Ccphalich, Rotterdam. ZIERIKZEE, 2 Jan.; Hans Georg, Godekop, New-York n. Rott. EMDEN, 31 Dcc; Clasiena, Dik, Koningsb. n. Leer, wegens ijsgang. OUXHAVEN. 1 Jan.; ter reede: Oceaan, v. Slooten, n. Rosano.- Redite, Stuit, Fernainbuck. ELSENEUR, 30 Dcc; Hollander, S., Petersb. n. Rott. LONDEN, 31 Dcc; Hallurn, Lukje, Holmstad. MARGATE,3I Dcc; Grietje $■ Funke, Wiersma, Groningen n. Chester. _ _ PORTLAND, 31 Dec-, Northern Queen, Scott, Rott. n. Cardiff; is van Lizard tot hier teruggestreven. - Alexander Bach, Tominich, Odessa n. Rott. PLYMOUTH, 30 Dcc; Annette, Wenninga, Rott. n. Cardiff. FALMOUTH, 30 Dcc; Samuel, Owen, Akyab; met gescheurde stengen. — 1 Jan.; Ada, Fallshaw, Mexilones. - Abandi, Ysasi, Havana. NEWPORT, 28 Dcc; Agatha, Zeijlinga, Gloucester. GLOUCESTER, 31 Dcc; Roelfina Tydens, Jansen, Delfzijl. SHIELDS, 31 Dcc; Alida, Jensen, Rott. - Antje, Schotten», Londen. SUNDERLAND, 31 Dcc; Vixen, Twelong, Rott. MIDDLESBRO, 31 Dec. 5 Sisters, Lowery, Amst. St. NAZAIRE, 27 Dcc; Annachiena Harmina, Zuidema, Petersburg. — 30 Dcc; Minerve, Gilbert, Rott. CADIX, 26 Dcc; Jantina Margaretha, Vos Peper, Cardiff. ALICANTE, 23 Dec. Mina, Hartman, Gibraltar. GENUA, 27 Dcc; Omega, de Boer, Amst. LIVORNO, 26 Dcc; Vlaardingen, vanden Boogcrt, Vlaardingen. TRIEST, 28 Dcc; Henderika, Pybes, Hamb. —29 Dec-, Tné&apos;st,</p>
</text>
